okay I guess we're ready to go I'm happy
好吧，我想我们已经准备好了，我很高兴
to be here it's the last session of
在这里，这是上一届会议
today I think before we go to the JCB
今天我想在我们去JCB之前
party so no hard feeling so put all
聚会，所以没有难过的感觉，所以把所有
probably the one who keep keep you
可能是那个一直保留你的人
between you and your beer tonight with
在你和你今晚的啤酒之间
that let's see I'll keep it very
让我们看看我会保持非常
informal so just shoot questions
非正式的，所以只问问题
whenever you want if we don't get
如果我们想要的话，只要您想要
further on to the first slide that's
继续到第一张幻灯片
good if I get to the end of the slide
如果我到达幻灯片的结尾，那很好
act that's also good but it's not
表现也不错，但事实并非如此
necessarily I'll do some code em was
我一定要做一些代码
rather than showing slides if you if you
而不是显示幻灯片，如果您
rolled like that
像那样滚动
I am a Java champion
我是Java冠军
I've been Coney Java since the inception
自成立以来我一直是Coney Java
of the language I'm in the executive
我在执行官中使用的语言
committee in the JCP and also served in
JCP的委员会，也曾在
the expert work for for embassy since
从那时起，为使馆工作的专家
its beginning and earlier this year I
从今年初开始
took over a suspect lead for this
为此接管了可疑的线索
specification I also serve on the the
我也曾在
expert group for jsr 375 which is a Java
Java的jsr 375专家组
EE security this is about the the
EE安全性是关于
embassy specification so what I'll go
使馆详细说明，我该怎么办
through today is a little bit about the
到今天为止，关于
status what we have done what's happened
状态我们所做的事情
how how come we we arrived where we are
我们如何到达我们所在的地方
today and I'll go through the basics of
今天，我将讲解
embassy and then I'll run some code
使馆，然后我将运行一些代码
demos and do some coding and show how
演示并进行一些编码，并展示如何
it's done and hopefully inspire you to
它已经完成，并希望启发您
try it out and and get feedback to us
试试看并获得反馈给我们
and see that we're on right Rackham and
看到我们在右边的Rackham和
I was going so the status of 371
我要去的状态是371
remember this one from last year that
还记得去年的那个
was when Oracle announced that they want
当甲骨文宣布他们想要
to drop them with a and I discussed it
用a删除它们，我讨论了
with some people at Oracle and we were
和Oracle的一些人一起
kind of annoyed that we couldn't
有点生气，我们不能
continue with this because we were
继续这个，因为我们
almost done
快完成了
I mean the spec documents was
我的意思是规格文件是
brilliantly written already so so it's
出色的写作已经如此
not very much
不是很多
left until we're there we only need to
离开，直到我们在那里，我们只需要
write the tzk more or less so that they
或多或少地写tzk，以便他们
didn't drop it entirely as they did with
没有像他们那样完全放弃
JMS and and and the the management a
JMS and和管理
source so we discussed and in January
来源，因此我们在1月进行了讨论
they actually proposed to transfer it to
他们实际上建议将其转移到
the community and we had ballot in AEC
社区，我们在AEC中进行了投票
and voted for a transfer of the spec
并投票同意转让规格
specification from Oracle to me so here
Oracle给我的规范，所以在这里
I am the new spec laid of embassy since
我是使馆的新规范
the ballot was approved in January the
投票于一月份获得批准
actual document with atomic urines
带有原子尿的实际文件
signature on was received in in May so
5月收到签名，所以
it took about four months to go through
大约花了四个月的时间
the process of actually having the
实际拥有
transfer finalized so and or model is
转移最终定为and and model is
controller or control to the community
社区的控制者或控制者
or for the community so this is a
或对于社区来说，这是一个
community it's a specification it's all
社区这是一个规范
open source we wanted to have community
我们想要拥有社区的开源
members contribute and and we want to
成员做出贡献，我们希望
give it back to the community and I'll
把它还给社区，我会
talk about that later as well the race
稍后再谈比赛
strong community supports there are
有强大的社区支持
eight or last I checked there are eight
八个或最后我检查了八个
user groups around the world who are
世界各地的用户组
supporting this chase or in the adopted
支持此追逐或被采纳
JSTOR program and there probably are
JSTOR程序，可能有
more to come because even though the
更多的来，因为即使
trend today is to ship the headless
今天的趋势是出货无头
arrest a PRS in micro service based
逮捕基于微服务的PRS
cloud environments you need to have some
云环境，您需要一些
UI and there is a market for a
用户界面，并且有一个市场
server-side rendered us as well and this
服务器端也使我们受益，这
is a very viable option to JSF for
对于JSF来说是一个非常可行的选择
example so we if you look at the
例子，所以我们如果你看
timeline we started this JSTOR back in
时间线，我们重新开始了这个JSTOR
2014 and and it was approved and
2014年，并获得批准，
followed the the regular status and and
遵循常规状态，并且
it was pretty fast out with a needy or
有需要的人很快就离开了
one and a day or two around Java one in
围绕Java一两天
since that the activity officially kind
从那以后，活动正式开始
of stopped
的已停止
and this was kind of the hiatus in Java
这就是Java中的中断
EE 8 but a couple of members of the Java
EE 8，但Java的几个成员
over the XM group and a couple of non
在XM小组和几个非
expert group members continued to
专家组成员继续
discuss on and off the mailing list and
讨论邮寄清单的内容，以及
delivered functionality and did evolve
提供功能并不断发展
the specification even though in this
即使在此规格
silent period and some of those guys
沉默期，其中一些人
were actually added to the expert group
实际上被添加到专家组中
later as well so it wasn't totally
后来也是如此，这不是完全
dormant it was slowly moving forward but
处于休眠状态，它正在缓慢前进，但是
we are still doing something and it was
我们仍在做某事，那是
community contributions at all it so and
社区的贡献
then at JavaOne it was announced to be
然后在JavaOne宣布
dropped and the transfer ballot in
掉了，转移了选票
January and here we are
一月，我们在这里
so what we've done since then is that
所以从那以后我们要做的是
the transfer was approved by the
转让获得了
executive committee in January the
一月执行委员会
transfer was finalized in May we set up
转让已于5月成立
a new infrastructure on github and we've
github上的新基础架构，我们已经
changed the license so this is a and
更改了许可证，所以这是一个
also I sore about that one we have moved
我也为我们搬家感到伤心
from Java and net to get up we did it
从Java和网络开始，我们做到了
before
之前
Javad enacted was closed down we've also
颁布的Javad已被关闭，我们也
moved the issues and over we set up a
移动了问题，然后我们建立了一个
new website and we revise the schedule
新网站，我们会修改时间表
and what we need to do is to formally or
我们需要做的是正式或
use more of the resources in the the add
使用添加中的更多资源
of the J's our program and get people to
J的课程
contribute a little bit more than than
贡献超过
and we are able to do today so
我们今天能够做到
so what are we done is to license it to
所以我们要做的是将其许可给
Apache to write license it's fully open
Apache写许可证完全开放
source all of it and that includes the
来源全部，其中包括
reference implementation which we call
我们称为参考实施
Ozark and the TCK so we are we open
Ozark和TCK，所以我们开放了
sourced the tyskie in May as Oracle is
甲骨文于5月份收购了tyskie
doing with their technologies coming up
他们的技术不断发展
now with the move to the Eclipse
现在转向Eclipse
formation so what about the adopted
形成，那么采用
JSTOR program what you look when you
JSTOR程序在您看起来像什么时
contribute with to help us with this
为帮助我们做出贡献
chair Sora
椅子索拉
well first of all just write code use it
首先，只需编写代码即可使用它
and try it out and see where are we
尝试一下，看看我们在哪里
doing things right and where is this
做正确的事，这在哪里
of lacking is it something you want in
缺乏是你想要的东西吗
or is it something you want out it's
还是你想要的东西
it's all open because we haven't
都是开放的，因为我们还没有
finalized it yet so give us feedback
完成它，所以给我们反馈
what we should do is something good or
我们应该做的是一件好事，或者
bad blog about it tweet about it show
关于它的坏博客关于它的推文显示
that you care it's good things what we
您关心的是好事
also need is actually somebody who is a
实际上也需要有人
creative kind of person who can create
有创造力的人可以创造
us a logo type because when we launch we
我们是徽标类型，因为当我们启动时
want to have a cake and we want the cake
要吃蛋糕，我们要蛋糕
that is looking better than the jsf cake
比jsf蛋糕看起来更好
that they had at the java land in in
他们在JAVA岛的土地
March so so and the JSF logo is open
如此进行，JSF徽标已打开
sourced contributed by members and voted
来源由成员贡献并投票
for in the expert Griffin we won't do
因为在专家格里芬我们不会
the same thing the only logos are being
同一件事是唯一的徽标
validation and security specification so
验证和安全规范，因此
all having them but we don't so if
都有他们，但如果不是
anyone wants to draw something and
任何人都想画点东西
please do you will be laces at a
请你把鞋带
contributor at the spec document if you
规范文档的贡献者，如果您
do so that's the easy way if you can use
这样做是您可以使用的简便方法
a pencil so that's about what I want to
一支铅笔，这就是我想要的
say about the the roadmap and what's
说说路线图以及什么
going on and what's not going on and etc
发生了什么，没有发生什么，等等
so let's move on to what's in it so
所以让我们继续前进吧
first of all MSE is an action-based MSE
首先，MSE是基于动作的MSE
framework by action-based we mean that
通过基于行动的框架，我们的意思是
the controller is defined by the
控制器由
application and not by the the framework
应用程序而不是框架
and there are no standard java ee
而且没有标准的Java EE
implementations of this today you have
今天的实现
non-standard and other implementations
非标准和其他实现
such as spring and receive for example
例如春天和接收例如
but there are no standardized in in the
但其中没有标准化
java ecosystem so if we look at a pretty
Java生态系统，所以，如果我们看一个漂亮的
common visualization of the MVC pattern
MVC模式的常见可视化
you typically have a request coming in
您通常会收到一个请求
from a browser the hits your controller
从浏览器中命中您的控制器
and the controller of there's a model
还有那个模型的控制器
and selects the view which access the
并选择访问
model to render the view and in a
模型以呈现视图并在
components based embassy such as JSF the
基于组件的使馆，例如JSF
controller is defined by the framework
控制器由框架定义
you know you have the faces servlet in
你知道你有faces servlet在
in Joseph so so us the developer only
在约瑟夫，所以我们只是开发商
implements the view and and the model
实现视图和模型
and in an action is Emma's Asia such as
在行动上，艾玛（Emma）的亚洲
mac-10
mac-10
the controller is defined by the
控制器由
application so you as the developer have
应用程序，因此您作为开发人员
total control over their controller and
完全控制他们的控制器
and so it's a more fine-grained a way of
所以这是一种更细粒度的方法
implementing things other action-based
实施其他基于动作的事物
are as I mentioned a spring embassy and
正如我提到的春天使馆
also stretch 2 if you remember that one
如果你还记得那一个，也伸展2
so one of the important objectives when
所以当一个重要目标
we started this specification was to
我们开始这个规范是为了
utilize the existing Java EE
利用现有的Java EE
technologies so if the we're something
技术，如果我们是某物
we could use we should use it rather
我们可以使用我们应该使用它
than invent something and example of
比发明一些东西和例子
this are to use CDI a bean validation
这是使用CDI进行bean验证
JPA for for the model implementations
JPA用于模型实现
and for the views use whatever we have
对于视图，请使用我们拥有的任何内容
such as actually facelets and jsps or
例如facelets和jsps或
other templates but the the focus was to
其他模板，但重点是
use the the existing technologies asks
使用现有技术要求
the requirements and for the controller
要求和对控制器的要求
there actually is isn't anything we can
其实我们无能为力
use directly so we have to to implement
直接使用，因此我们必须实施
something or build something on top of
在某物之上或之上构建某物
some of the existing technologies that
一些现有技术
brought us to some key decisions or
带给我们一些关键的决定，或者
actually one key decision in the expert
实际上是专家的一项关键决定
group pretty early
小组很早
there were divided but we we came to a
有分歧，但我们来到了
a conclusion that we want to build MVC
我们想要构建MVC的结论
on top of jax-rs
在jax-rs之上
the alternative would be to build on top
替代方案是建立在顶部
of servlets which also would have made
的servlet也会
sense and most or jax-rs can also be
感觉，大多数或jax-rs也可以是
implemented on top of servlet so so in
在servlet之上实现，所以在
either way it's it's it's a good choice
无论哪种方式，这都是一个不错的选择
so the jax-rs was selected after vote we
因此，jax-rs在投票后被选中
were divided in a group but personally I
被分成一组，但我个人
think it's a good choice and especially
认为这是一个不错的选择，尤其是
as today you see Jack psoriasis is a
就像今天您看到的杰克牛皮癣是
very much used technology for writing in
非常常用的书写技术
westerns and faces and to use that
西方人和面孔，并使用它
knowledge is one of the benefits of the
知识是
mac-10 so we start start to look at
mac-10，所以我们开始看看
looking at the controller's done so if
查看控制器的操作，如果
we start with a simple class in this
我们从一个简单的类开始
case called hello controller this name
这种情况称为hello controller
is not necessarily a very good name and
不一定是一个很好的名字，
I'll come back to that in a minute the
一分钟后，我会回到
first thing we do to to you know step to
我们要做的第一件事就是知道
creating an MC controller here is to add
在这里创建MC控制器是为了添加
the a path annotation and as patent is a
路径注释，作为专利，是
Jack's orientation so so far we're only
到目前为止，杰克的定位只是
using jacks or jacks or s and this is
使用千斤顶或千斤顶或s，这是
the the add path for hello them and then
为他们打招呼的添加路径，然后
we had the F control orientation to this
我们对此有F控制取向
one and this tells the the container
一个，这告诉容器
that this is not a jax-rs resource this
这不是jax-rs资源，
is a controller in an MVC and it will do
是MVC中的控制器，它将执行
behave a little bit differently and the
表现有些不同，
important thing here is that in this
这里重要的是
example I'll put the controller on the
示例我将控制器放在
class level and that means that every
班级，这意味着每个
method that has a public method and so
具有公共方法的方法等等
called one of these checks for us at
叫我们其中一张支票
path or at get at post etcetera our
路径或到达后等我们
controllers so my class isn't the
控制器，所以我的课不是
controller that's why the name isn't
这就是为什么控制器名称不正确的原因
very good here because it's actually a
这里很好，因为它实际上是
controller controller and then every
控制器控制器，然后每个
method is actually the controller
方法实际上是控制器
you can also put the at control
您也可以控制
orientation on method level and that
方法层面的方向
means that you can actually mix and
表示您实际上可以混合并
match a rest resource with in MSE
与MSE中的其余资源匹配
controller and actually have everything
控制器，实际上拥有一切
in one class if you want to do it
如果你想一堂课
whether that's a good idea or not that
不管这是一个好主意
probably depends on your special use
可能取决于您的特殊用途
case so that's basically the very
案例，所以基本上
simplest a controller in missy it's just
Missy中最简单的控制器
one annotation on on a dexterous
一个灵巧的注解
resource let's go on with the views we
资源让我们继续我们的观点
have our controller us with defined in a
将我们的控制器定义为
couple of slides ago and then we add the
几张幻灯片，然后我们添加
act get annotation which is jax-rs for
行为获取注释，它是jax-rs的
saying this is a ship we get requests
说这是我们接到请求的船
and in this case we return a string the
在这种情况下，我们返回一个字符串
method name is is hello in this case and
在这种情况下，方法名称是hello并且
we return hello.js b and this is where
我们返回hello.js b，这就是
it where the F control orientation
它在F控制方向
actually does its magic because usually
实际上是在做魔术，因为通常
if you did this in the jacks or as a
如果您是在千斤顶中或作为
resource you would return the string
资源，您将返回字符串
hello JSP but since the app control
你好JSP但由于应用程序控制
orientation there it behaves differently
那里的方向不同
and actually returns the view that hello
并实际上返回了视图
JSP renders and the default location of
JSP渲染和默认位置
this view this JSP files page is in the
此JSP文件页面的视图位于
debian views folder in your web
您网络中的debian views文件夹
application and i'll show you a little
应用程序，我会告诉你一点
later
后来
I show Jay SPS here we also support
我在这里向我们展示Jay SPS，我们也支持
facelets that's needed by the
所需的方面
specification and in addition to that
规格及其他
our reference information also support
我们的参考信息也支持
finally free market massages loss today
今天终于自由市场按摩损失
and etc I think also we actually support
等我想我们也确实支持
ask a dog and I think there are about 12
问一只狗，我想大约有十二只
different rendering engines that we
我们使用的不同渲染引擎
support and those are community
支持，这些都是社区
contributed by people in the expert
由专家人士提供
group and however the exit group we also
组，但是退出组，我们也
have a lot of flexibility and this is
有很大的灵活性，这是
where we we we are thinking of actually
我们在想什么
removing something
去除东西
if it doesn't make sense to have this
如果没有这个意义
flexibility because as I saw in a
灵活性，因为正如我在
previous slide we you can return a
上一张幻灯片，我们可以返回一个
string with just the the hello JSP the
字符串与您好JSP
name of the review you can also return a
评论的名称，您还可以返回
viewable object and then it can actually
可见的对象，然后它实际上可以
subclass this and do whatever and and
将此子类化并执行任何操作，并
implement it yourself so it adds some
自己实施，这样就增加了一些
flexibility if you want that you can
灵活性，如果您希望可以
also go a really low level and actually
也走得很低，实际上
use a Jack stress response class and and
使用Jack压力响应类，然后
just have the entity being the hello.js
只是实体是hello.js
pin all these are equivalent the render
固定所有这些都是等效的
the same view and we also added an @
相同的视图，我们还添加了一个@
viewer annotation so you can have a void
查看器注释，因此您可以留空
return a method return void and that's
返回一个方法，返回void，那是
not allowed in jax-rs
jax-rs中不允许
so this annotation makes that possible
所以这个注释使这成为可能
and after you has another benefit and
在您获得另一个好处之后，
that is if you have a controller class
那就是如果你有一个控制器类
or a class with a lot of controller
或具有很多控制器的类
methods that all render the same view
都呈现相同视图的方法
you can set this at V orientation on
您可以将其设置为V向
class level as you would do with a
班级水平，就像您使用
controller and those reduce the
控制器和那些减少
boilerplate and write write less
样板写少写
so over two models and in in models we
因此，在两个模型中以及在模型中
leverage CDI so in this case we have a
利用CDI，因此在这种情况下，
greeting object which is request scoped
请求范围的问候对象
in this case we leverage all serious
在这种情况下，我们会认真对待所有
copes and this has the getter and setter
应付，这有吸气剂和二传手
is just a plain old Java object and the
只是一个普通的旧Java对象，
way you use it is if you have this
您使用它的方式是如果您有这个
controller level created in a previous
在先前版本中创建的控制器级别
that renders the hello JSP view you can
可以呈现Hello JSP视图
just simply inject your your greeting
只是简单地打个招呼
class into this controller and then you
类到这个控制器，然后你
will be able to access it and and for
将能够访问它，并且对于
example set the message in your
在您的示例中设置消息
controller method or do whatever you you
控制器方法或您所做的任何事情
are doing with your model there and then
在那边做你的模型，然后
from the view you can access a model by
从视图中，您可以通过以下方式访问模型
using expression language so this was
使用表达语言，所以这是
the the CDI approach we also support a
CDI方法我们也支持
non CDI version of it in case your view
非CDI版本，以防您查看
engine doesn't support CDI you have the
引擎不支持CDI，您拥有
same controller so everything is the
相同的控制器，所以一切都是
same there and rather than injecting a
在那里一样，而不是注入一个
greetings CDI scope object you inject a
您注入的问候CDI范围对象
models object and models is a class
模型对象和模型是一类
provided by MSE specification and the
由MSE规范和
the reason it's called models and not
被称为模型而不是模型的原因
model is to avoid collision with another
模式是避免与另一个碰撞
class called model in Java EE so so what
类在Java EE中称为模型
you do here it is basically a hash map
你在这里做这基本上是一个哈希图
so we just put the the stuff you one of
所以我们只是把你的东西之一
the areas Atlanta I've been lazy and not
在亚特兰大我一直很懒惰的地方
updated slice but they could be in San
更新了切片，但它们可能在San
Francisco and then you put the the the
弗朗西斯科，然后你把
message on on on the model and you can
消息在模型上，您可以
access this is the same way from the via
通过via访问这是相同的方式
so let's look at some code
让我们来看一些代码
I did an upgrade to High Sierra last
我上次升级到High Sierra
night and that is not nothing I wouldn't
晚上，那不是什么，我不会
recommend it if you haven't talked the
如果您还没聊过，就推荐它
day after I couldn't log into my
我无法登录后一天
computer afterwards so luckily I had an
后来我很幸运地有一台电脑
admin account check you again reset my
管理员帐户再次检查您重设我的帐户
password rotates it works so let's look
密码旋转有效，让我们来看看
at some of the code here and I've
在这里的一些代码中，我已经
created a very simple a simple project
创建了一个非常简单的简单项目
here and what i'm doing here is i'll
在这里，我在这里要做的是
just show you how you set it up with the
只是向您展示如何使用
form files and everything to get started
表格文件以及一切入门
and we won't show any more profiles so
我们不会再显示任何个人资料，因此
we rely on on a Java Web API in this
我们在此依赖于Java Web API
case I actually run on on Java EE 8 so
我实际上在Java EE 8上运行的情况
I'll be running it demos on GlassFish 5
我将在GlassFish 5上运行它的演示
we also support Java 87 so so you're
我们还支持Java 87，所以您
fine with either but in this case I'll
可以，但在这种情况下，我会
run on glassfish 5 and also some other
在glassfish 5和其他一些设备上运行
servers so you need to have the provided
服务器，因此您需要提供
web app AI or the full API of Java EE
网络应用程序AI或Java EE的完整API
and then you had the the MSE API
然后您有了MSE API
dependency and in my case I we support a
依赖性，就我而言，我们支持
Jersey and rustici so I've just created
泽西岛和拉斯蒂尼，所以我刚刚创建了
profiles for it for to make it clear
为了使它清晰的配置文件
here so if I'm running in GlassFish or
如果我在GlassFish中运行或
any any server that comes to Jersey I
来到Jersey I的任何服务器
add the Oh Sarge or say dependency and
添加Oh Sarge或说依赖性，
if I run with for example our flower
例如，如果我带着我们的花跑
which comes with birthday say I had the
生日那天说我有
procedure depends there so these two
程序取决于那里，所以这两个
dependencies you need to need to have
您需要具有的依赖项
the API and you need to have the
API，并且您需要
reference implementation and that is
参考实施，那就是
because we're not a part of Java EE but
因为我们不是Java EE的一部分，但是
we rely on on Java EE technologies I
我们依靠Java EE技术
also have some profiles here for setting
在这里也有一些配置文件
it up in docker I'll run some demos in
在docker中，我将在其中运行一些演示
that afterwards but that's not the focus
那之后，但这不是重点
of this talk
这个谈话
so let's look at my controller class for
所以让我们看一下我的控制器类
first of all you said it you set up the
首先，您说要建立
the application the same way you would
该应用程序与您将使用的相同方式
do with a dexterous application because
使用灵巧的应用程序，因为
we're basing on jax-rs so I'm using all
我们基于jax-rs，所以我正在使用所有
dexterous here with the application
灵巧的与应用程序
class and the application path and and
类和应用程序路径以及
just add my controller attitude we do
只需添加我的控制器态度即可
then Ajax resource and my controller is
然后Ajax资源和我的控制器是
super simple
超级简单
it just says returners hello JSP so
它只是说返回者你好JSP所以
nothing there and my view is put it in
那里什么都没有，我的观点就放在里面
the web use folder and is also just
网络使用文件夹，也只是
saying hellos of the world so if I run
向世界打招呼，所以如果我跑步
this one you would expect it should say
您期望它应该说
hello world and it does so it's no magic
世界，你好，这不是魔术
there we're not doing any anything cool
那里我们什么都没做
yet so let's do something and for
但是，让我们做点什么
example go in here and inject the models
示例进入这里并注入模型
like this and maybe say model that's
这样，也许说模型是
message and one this and then just
消息和一个然后然后
returned the JSP ssibly
明智地返回了JSP
and in interview I could say rather than
在采访中我可以说而不是
saying hello world older message so now
说你好世界较旧的消息，所以现在
I should have a getro guest coming into
我应该有个客人来
my my path that hello or to set the the
我的路径，你好或设置
message on the model and return the same
消息在模型上并返回相同
view as I did previously I said run this
像我之前说的那样查看
one you should say hello job one so now
一个你应该打个招呼吧
I'm actually interacting with the model
我实际上是在与模型互动
from my view such that it goes a little
在我看来，这有点
bit further and I prepared a nother here
再远一点，我在这里准备了一个
I'll just run it to begin with so you'll
我将首先运行它，以便您
see it's doing exactly the same as the
看到它的作用与
stuff we're doing what I've added here
我们正在做的事情我在这里添加了
is one more view a a form that is just
是另一个视图，只是
doing a post of the name to give the
做一个名字的职位给
controller and my hello controller is
控制器，我的控制器是
exactly the same so what I want to do
完全一样，所以我想做什么
here is that when I when I access this
这是当我访问此文件时
page I want to have a input field where
我想在其中输入字段的页面
I can write my name and then have it to
我可以写下我的名字然后
say hello to my name so what I'll do
跟我打个招呼，我该怎么办
here is to rather than return the the
这里是而不是返回
the hello page I'll return the the form
您好，我将返回表单
and run it
并运行它
so now it says it renders different view
所以现在说它呈现了不同的视图
it's the same reakless going down to the
毫无顾忌地下降到
controller or it's the same controller
控制器或它是同一控制器
or handling it but there's another view
或处理它，但还有另一种观点
rendering so if I have for example right
渲染，所以如果我有例如正确的
dick and submit it it was a method of
迪克并提交它是一种方法
love because I haven't implemented
爱，因为我还没有实现
anything to handle a post yet so this is
什么都可以处理帖子，所以这是
all as expected so what does she do is
一切都如预期，所以她要做的是
to add another method and use the add
添加另一种方法并使用添加
post from from dexterous and let's use a
来自灵巧的帖子，让我们使用
void here like this and it doesn't do
像这样在这里无效，它没有做
anything so let's add an annotation and
任何东西，让我们添加一个注释，
render the hello JSP so now when I get a
渲染Hello JSP，所以现在当我得到一个
post it should be handled with this
发布它应该与此处理
method and returned the the hello page
方法并返回问候页面
so if I run this one again still say
所以如果我再运行一次
look to do I submit it and it renders an
看起来我提交它，它呈现
empty page and that's because I haven't
空页，那是因为我还没有
done any updates to the model yet so
尚未对模型进行任何更新
what I have to do is actually to take
我要做的实际上是服用
this message here and do that when I do
这条消息在这里，当我这样做时
the post if I then run it it should say
该职位，如果我然后运行它应该说
hello hello did you have one even though
你好，你有没有
I say do care and he says hello to jovan
我说要小心，他向乔万问好
because it's requests go to everything
因为这是一切的要求
right this is per request but I don't
对，这是每个请求，但我没有
want to say hello to job one I mean it's
想打个招呼，我的意思是
Duke I'm putting insert it's Duke I want
我要插入的公爵是我想要的公爵
to say hello to so let's access whatever
向您问好，让我们访问任何内容
I get to this form and then I can use
我进入此表格，然后我可以使用
the the form purim jax-rs annotation and
表单purim jax-rs批注和
it is in a name attribute in in my view
它在我看来是在name属性中
it's called
被称为
name here
在这里命名
so and this is a string name so here I
所以，这是一个字符串名称，所以我在这里
get the the name from the form and then
从表单中获取名称，然后
I can rather than saying hello to job
我可以跟工作打招呼而不是
one I can say ho hello to name right so
我可以说一声打招呼
I'm using the input ID ID it's not very
我正在使用输入的ID ID，它不是很
advanced but still um I'm just getting
先进，但我还是得到了
what I get from the form so now I say
我从表格中得到什么，所以现在我说
hello Duke this is how it works
你好公爵这是怎么运作的
so I also said that we have some other
所以我也说我们还有其他一些
cool small features and say that you
很棒的小功能，说你
want to have some security added to this
想要为此添加一些安全性
this post over this form for example
例如，此表格上的帖子
protect yourself for cross-site request
保护自己以应对跨站点请求
forgery then we have a simple annotation
伪造的话，我们有一个简单的注释
we can add here and say that we want
我们可以在这里添加并说我们想要
this to be CSRs F valid so by adding
这是有效的CSR，因此添加
this annotation I'm explicitly saying
我明确地说这个注释
that this HT request should be validated
应该验证此HT请求
for cross-site request forgery I could
对于跨站点请求伪造我可以
do it by setting a property and have it
通过设置一个属性并拥有它
implicitly that all methods are going to
隐含地，所有方法都将
be it this is the explicit way and the
是这是明确的方式，
way I configure that is to set a
我配置的方法是设置一个
property and when I configure it the
属性，当我配置它时
application so then I can set the get
应用程序，这样我就可以设置get
properties and here is I set the
属性，这是我设置的
prediction to to be explicit
预测要明确
so so if I now run it what do you expect
所以，如果我现在运行它，您期望什么
will happen right in Duke submit it but
会在杜克提交时发生，但是
it doesn't show anything don't say if
它没有显示任何内容，不说是否
that's correct that's a nice one there
没错，那是一个不错的选择
see I get a a 400 bad request error you
看到我收到AA 400错误请求错误消息
would expected it to be a foreigner 3
希望它是外国人3
not allowed but that that depends on on
不允许，但这取决于
the the implementation I think run
我认为运行的实现
anything Wallflower tours and we'll look
任何Wallflower之旅，我们都会期待
at it there what I should do to to avoid
在那儿我应该避免
this thing is that in my form I actually
这件事是我的形式
need to add this CSRF token that is
需要添加的CSRF令牌是
generated from the server so why not
从服务器生成的，为什么不呢
access the controller and renders this
访问控制器并呈现此
view this token is set in my form and is
查看此令牌已设置在我的表单中，并且
valid until the next request so this is
有效期至下一个请求，因此
just an way of doing it and the way I do
只是一种方式和我的方式
this is that I use the the embassy
这是我使用使馆
context which I also can access here in
我也可以在这里访问的上下文
in my my by injecting it in my class and
通过将其注入我的班级中
was a context so I can also actually use
是一个上下文，所以我也可以实际使用
it in in my method here too to extract
它在我的方法中也可以提取
information from it for example get CSRF
从中获取信息，例如获取CSRF
if I want to check if that's valid and
如果我想检查是否有效，并且
do some coding on it on server side so
在服务器端对此进行一些编码，以便
what will happen now when I run it is
现在，当我运行它时会发生什么
that now I've set the token in my form
现在我已经在表单中设置了令牌
and I'm validating on the server so when
我正在服务器上验证
I submit Derrick it will say hello dick
我提交Derrick，它会说你好，迪克
so let's also check for four we also
所以我们还要检查四个
have some simple language support or
有一些简单的语言支持或
internationalization so I've already
国际化，所以我已经
injected the MSA contexts so so what I
注入了MSA上下文，所以我
can do here is to take the MSE context
这里可以做的就是采用MSE上下文
and get like locale and get language for
并像语言环境一样获取语言
example and I can just say spring
例子，我只能说春天
language is so I get the language from
语言是，所以我从
the the MSE context and then I can I can
MSE上下文，然后我可以
just add here maybe you know in which
只需在这里添加，也许您知道其中
language Shaw I'm saying hello in or I
语言Shaw我在打招呼，或者我
could actually have a language string
可能实际上有一个语言字符串
which will be a natural thing to do but
这是很自然的事情，但是
in this demo I'll just do that yes if I
在这个演示中，如果我会
now say do care I submit it and I say
现在说要小心我提交并说
hello do it in English and that is
你好用英语做，那就是
because I'm here or mi brazo said in
因为我在这里或mi brazo说
English so if I go into here and set a
英语，所以如果我进入这里并设置一个
nother language for example they're set
例如他们设定的其他语言
it to Klingon for example just disable
例如将其禁用到Klingon
this and do the same thing go there and
这并做同样的事情去那里，
say do care and submit Oh
说要照顾好并提交哦
right
对
they're enable so now it's all think so
他们启用，所以现在所有人都这么认为
now it should say hello in in some
现在它应该在某些地方打个招呼
different language so it's a detected
不同的语言，因此被检测到
language in a browser and the the
浏览器中的语言和
default implementation which comes with
附带的默认实现
the reference implication is that you
参考含义是
take it from the language header in the
从中的语言标题中获取
HTTP request but you can also provide
HTTP请求，但您也可以提供
your your own language provider in and
您自己的语言提供商，并且
and figure it out whatever you want to
并找出你想要的
do if it's from the URL structure if you
如果它来自URL结构，则执行
add like German or English in front or
在前面加上德语或英语
in the back of the URL you can you can
在网址的后面，您可以
just implement very simply that a
只是非常简单地实现
language provider to figure out which
语言提供者找出哪个
language it is there is another cool
语言是另一种酷
thing we have and that is events so we
我们拥有的东西就是事件，所以我们
have added support for a number of
增加了对
events so if I have a kind of a private
事件，如果我有一个私人的
mind and here I can use
介意，在这里我可以使用
CDI servers and for example the after
CDI服务器，例如
controller events so this is a event
控制器事件，所以这是一个事件
that will fired after the controller has
在控制器执行完后会触发
been invoked and I can just do whatever
被调用，我可以做任何事情
I want here
我要在这里
sorry it has a CDI event but the after
对不起，它有一个CDI事件，但之后
controller event is from MSI yes so we
控制器事件来自MSI是的，所以我们
have we have four five different events
我们有四个五个不同的事件吗
defined it's the after controller it's
定义它是after控制器
after process view event before
流程查看事件之前
controller before process view and
过程视图之前的控制器和
controller redirect event so we have
控制器重定向事件，所以我们有
five events defined and currently I'm
定义了五个事件，目前我是
actually not sure if we by default
实际上不确定我们是否默认
support asynchronous events since we're
支持异步事件，因为我们
running on Syria too I think we need to
我也想在叙利亚跑
look at the implementation because these
看一下实现，因为这些
events if they are synchronous you
事件，如果它们是同步的
shouldn't do anything heavy lifting here
在这里不应该做任何繁重的工作
because then you will slow down your
因为那样你会减慢你的速度
application but what we can do now is if
应用程序，但是我们现在可以做的是
we decide that Java EE 8 is our baseline
我们认为Java EE 8是我们的基准
we can rely on on asynchronous events
我们可以依靠异步事件
and actually do that
并做到这一点
so this one should just be printing in
所以这应该只是打印
in the log when we do it stuff oh okay
在日志中，当我们这样做时，东西好吗
it looks like we have to do something
看来我们必须做点什么
for to be able to support see reality so
为了能够支持看到现实，所以
I want to show another thing that we
我想展示另一件事，我们
actually support Java EE right but for
实际上支持Java EE，但是对于
before that all this is running in
在这一切都在运行之前
GlassFish so I just wanted to show you
GlassFish，所以我只想告诉你
that we also support wild climb or other
我们也支持野外攀登或其他
in relation so let's go to
有关，所以我们去
[Music]
[音乐]
and they font up a little
他们加了一点字体
so this is reasonable
所以这是合理的
so if I build this on with the the
所以如果我用
docker profile for wildfire I would
我想要的野火的docker个人资料
Navin playin package docker build
Navin Playin软件包Docker构建
awesome docker I think I call that so
很棒的码头工人，我想我这么称呼
I'll just rebuild whatever I built now
我要重建我现在建造的任何东西
and just build a docker image of it
并为其构建一个docker镜像
based on wildfly 11 release candidates
基于wildfly 11版本候选
and then I should be able to run it
然后我应该可以运行它
there's some fire supply and in docker
有一些火力供应和码头工人
and my application there and I should be
和我的申请在那里，我应该是
ready to go local host 8080
准备去 localhost 8080
it really to this simple form there and
真的以这种简单的形式存在
it runs here and if I write dick it says
它在这里运行，如果我写鸡巴说
a lot to do in English so we actually
用英语做很多事情，所以我们实际上
support wildfly as well so we have a
也支持wildfly，所以我们有一个
reference information that supports
支持的参考信息
Jerseyan and Norris TC and the others
泽西岛和诺里斯TC等
should be fairly simple to write support
编写支持应该相当简单
for what I also have here want to show
我也想在这里展示
you is Java e8 support a little bit but
您对Java e8的支持有点
since we are supporting Java EE we
由于我们支持Java EE，因此我们
support bean validation so if I use the
支持bean验证，所以如果我使用
any email and say that the name of
任何电子邮件，并说
Symantec in the forum has to be an email
赛门铁克在论坛中必须是一封电子邮件
I can run this one again okay
我可以再运行一次
[Music]
[音乐]
I the reason why it didn't work is that
我之所以不起作用的原因是
since I build it income online with the
因为我使用
Wildflower profile I'm using the rest is
我正在使用的野花简介是
a version of it sir just have to make
先生的版本，只需要
sure that I fill it with the glass while
确保我在杯子里装满
a glassfish profile and then I should be
玻璃鱼的轮廓，然后我应该
able to run so here we go if I said dick
能够运行，所以如果我说迪克我们就去
now and submit it it will say a bad
现在提交它会说不好
request and that's because it's not an
请求，那是因为这不是
email and I'm not handling these errors
电子邮件，我没有处理这些错误
very aggressively so if I want to I see
非常激进，所以如果我想
we have only five minutes left so I
我们只剩下五分钟了，所以我
don't think I'll have time for it but if
不要以为我有时间
if I write a Duke at Java calm email or
如果我在Java电子邮件中写了Duke，或者
s it will work so he says valiree's I
它会起作用，所以他说瓦莱里是我
wasn't able to show you the the actual
无法向您展示实际
how you can handle this well this
你怎么能很好地处理这个
validation errors but we have a
验证错误，但我们有一个
fine-grained control and a pretty cool
细粒度的控制，非常酷
way to handle each of these validations
处理每个验证的方法
errors individually so let me just go
个别出错，所以让我走吧
back to my slides we're gonna be off
回到我的幻灯片，我们将要离开
today JP party soon so if you sum up its
今天JP党很快，所以如果你总结一下
action base time you see it
您看到的动作基准时间
that means you build the controller in
这意味着您在其中构建控制器
the application we build on existing
我们基于现有的应用程序
Java EE technologies and we also support
Java EE技术，我们也支持
Java EE 8 you also have a little bit
Java EE 8您也有一点
work maybe to look at you last see the I
工作也许要看你最后看到我
- no but
- 不是，但
we support the other pretty well we're
我们很好地支持另一个
built on top of jax-rs
建立在jax-rs之上
we support GlassFish and wildfly the
我们支持GlassFish和wildfly
plan going on for this specification is
该规范正在进行的计划是
that during the last part of this year
在今年下半年
we should be able to publish a public
我们应该能够公开发布
review then the plan is to have a
进行审核，然后计划是
proposed final draft in q1 next year and
明年第一季度的拟议最终草案，以及
hopefully have a final release q2 next
希望接下来发布最终版本q2
year so within six to eight months we
一年，所以在六到八个月内
should be able to find lastest
应该能够找到最新的
specification
规格
and currently we are in get up and we're
目前我们正在起床，我们正在
looking at the development with Java e
着眼于Java e的发展
or e fo J and it would be very natural
或e fo J，这很自然
for us to follow them to eclipse I don't
让我们跟随他们使我黯然失色
think we'll go there before I think they
认为我们会先去那里
should be able to set up the project
应该能够建立项目
just get it done but we will start the
只是完成它，但我们将开始
dialogue with them and and movies all
与他们和电影对话
three eclipses together with them and
与他们一起的三个月蚀和
hopefully we can have some way of being
希望我们可以有一些方式
incorporated into the Java EE or Evo
合并到Java EE或Evo中
echo system again the the project page
再次回显系统的项目页面
is M I suspect of the org we are on
是我们所在组织的MI嫌疑人
github we have the mo suspect
github我们有mo嫌疑人
organization there we are also currently
组织在那里，我们目前也
in the Java EE github organization and
在Java EE github组织中
we will be there until they move it to
我们将在那里，直到他们将其移至
github whether they actually move it and
github他们是否真的移动了
think that it's part of the Oracle code
认为这是Oracle代码的一部分
base or whatever I'm not sure what's
基地或其他我不确定是什么
gonna happen to this repo but we treat
会发生在这个仓库中，但我们会
it as a read-only mirror so whenever we
它作为只读镜像，所以无论何时我们
push something to our wrapper we just
将东西推到包装纸上
push to there as well so we don't do
也要推到那里，所以我们不做
anything the demos I showed here today
我今天在这里展示的任何演示
are on my github we also have demos on
在我的github上，我们也有演示
on the MSD organization we have a buff
在MSD组织上，我们有一个buff
tomorrow at 7:45 there I can show some
明天7:45我可以给大家看一些
more details about how to do the
有关如何操作的更多详细信息
validation stuff and we can discuss a
验证的东西，我们可以讨论一个
little bit I have to move forward I know
我必须前进一点，我知道
it's late tomorrow and there's probably
明天很晚，可能有
lots of parties going on then as well
还有很多聚会
but I hope some we will come there and
但我希望我们能来那里
we can go through it it's in this room
我们可以通过它在这个房间里
and so that's what I had don't forget to
这就是我所不能忘记的
vote when you go and it's a green deck
你去的时候投票，那是一个绿色的甲板
that but it's best to push but we feel
那是最好的选择，但是我们觉得
free to push the others as well we have
也可以自由地推动其他人
a couple of minutes for questions and if
几分钟问问题，如果
you want to want me to show you I can
你想让我告诉你我可以
show you the the website it looks pretty
向您展示漂亮的网站
ok this
好的这个
how the website looks a couple examples
该网站的外观示例
internet here but but it also links to
互联网在这里，但它也链接到
our Giro rep oh we're Oh Sark that's the
我们的转帐代表哦，我们是萨克
reference implication we have the
参考含义我们有
specification there our website the TCK
规格在我们的网站TCK
fully open open source approach to on
完全开放的开源方法
kirov we have some proposals where you
基洛夫我们有一些建议给您
can actually submit things you want to
可以实际提交您想要的东西
have introspect but we are not able to
有内省，但我们无法
do right now and we also probably put
现在就做，我们也可能把
some samples and tutorial software as
一些示例和教程软件
well so that's it
好吧就这样
questions one minute for question yes
一分钟问问题是
yes yes session scope for CDI we
是是CDI的会话范围
actually support a custom scope as well
实际上也支持自定义范围
we have defined our own scope for
我们已经定义了自己的范围
redirects so similar to flash scope in
重定向，类似于Flash作用域中的
spring MVC so so you can actually keep
Spring MVC，因此您实际上可以保持
the scope over beam if you implement the
如果您实施了
post redirect get pattern so the radar
发布重定向获取模式，以便雷达
scope will last for one one post and
范围将持续一个职位，并且
won't yet
还不会
yes
是
yeah yeah so the question is if the
是的，所以问题是
service request HTTP request is
服务请求HTTP请求为
available in an MC controller and the
可在MC控制器中使用
answer to that is it may or it may not
答案可能是，也可能不是
it depends on if the jax-rs
这取决于jax-rs
implementation are on top of servlet or
实现位于servlet或
not because jax-rs can be implemented
不是因为可以实现jax-rs
without servlets and then you won't have
没有servlet，那么您将没有
access to it so currently ozark is using
访问它，因此当前ozark正在使用
a little bit of sort of stuff so so and
有点像这样的东西
I think post rest easy and Jersey are
我认为休息很容易，泽西岛
based on servlet so we find there but
基于servlet，所以我们在那里找到了
you can actually have an implementation
你实际上可以有一个实现
that doesn't have the servlets so you
没有servlet，所以您
need to know where you are yeah in
需要知道你在哪里
Jersey you can but I don't think that
泽西岛可以，但我不认为
would work in other
会在其他工作
yes
是
I think that as if the jax-rs
我认为好像jax-rs
implementation you're using is based on
您正在使用的实现基于
servlet and so look for you would get it
servlet，所以您会发现它
for free the same
免费一样
yeah I would say that yes you have we
是的，我会说，是的，你有我们
have I didn't have time to show that
我没有时间证明这一点吗
today but I'll do that in in both show
今天，但我会在两个节目中都这样做
the validation we have because jax-rs
验证，因为jax-rs
comes with validation and supports bean
附带验证并支持bean
validation and if you you have like the
验证，如果您喜欢
email doesn't validate true jax-rs will
电子邮件无法验证真正的jax-rs是否可以
will throw an exception and and you can
将引发异常，您可以
have an exception mapper that handles it
有一个处理它的异常映射器
and does whatever you do and that's kind
做你所做的一切，这是一种
of like a one-size-fits-all catch it
就像一个大小适合所有
way of doing it and that's not
的方式，那不是
necessarily good for a MSE application
对MSE应用程序一定很好
where you want to have a little bit more
你想多一点
fine guys control and maybe populate a
好男人控制，也许填充
read something on the field that was
在田野上读了一些东西
actually not validated similarly so you
实际上没有经过类似的验证，所以您
want to redirect to the same form and
想要重定向到相同的表单，并且
say that hey the email field was not
说，嘿，电子邮件字段不是
filled correctly and and we have support
正确填写，我们有支持
for that by by getting the individual
为此，通过获得个人
and by bypassing the jax-rs exception
并绕过jax-rs异常
validation humbling and inject a binding
验证谦逊并注入绑定
result and use that in your form I'll
结果并以您的形式使用
show that tomorrow or yes
表明明天还是
[Music]
[音乐]
I think it's it's actually just
我认为是这样
extending hashmap so whatever you can
扩展哈希图，以便您可以
put in a hashmap you can use
放在可以使用的哈希图中
sorry
抱歉
have we explicitly said that inspect but
我们是否明确说过检查
then it's probably true I'm not sure I
那可能是真的，我不确定
have to check Tara
必须检查塔拉
yes I think we're past our time and
是的，我认为我们已经过去了，
ready for JCP thank you
准备好进行JCP谢谢
[Applause]
[掌声]